Ēmi kāvālō nākeruka lēdē svāmi
I don’t know what I want, O Lord.
Kāmituḍa nāku kaivalyamēdi
I seek desires, where is Moksha for me?
Ēmi kāvālō nākeruka lēdē svāmi
I don’t know what I want, O Lord.
Kāmituḍa nāku kaivalyamēdi
I seek desires, where is Moksha for me?
Dhanamule bahu saukhyamani talatu nā madilōna
I think that wealth is the great bliss in my mind.
Kanuka nīvē manassu gamyamen̄cavō
So, you please guide the direction of my mind
Kunuku lēka bhayamulandē gaḍipeḍi nā cittambunu
My mind always stays in fear without sleep
Tanuvu bhrānti mānpi tagulu jñānamīyavō
Please remove the ignorance of today and give me the suitable knowledge
Ēmi kāvālō nākeruka lēdē svāmi
I don’t know what I want, O Lord.
Kāmituḍa nāku kaivalyamēdi
I seek desires, where is Moksha for me?
Koluvule nija sukhamulani kōreda ninnē eppuḍu
I wish various influential positions from you
Niluvunā cīlci nāku nijamu telupavō
Break me and show me the truth
Naluvuri man̄nanalakoraku Narahari ninn̄erugakunṭi
I do not know you, seeking admiration from others
Caluvagu caraṇāla chāya śāntinīyavō
Please give me the peace in the shadow of your pleasant feet
Ēmi kāvālō nākeruka lēdē svāmi
I don’t know what I want, O Lord.
Kāmituḍa nāku kaivalyamēdi
I seek desires, where is Moksha for me?
Ēmi kāvālō nākeruka lēdē svāmi
I don’t know what I want, O Lord.
Kāmituḍa nāku kaivalyamēdi
I seek desires, where is Moksha for me?